

LANGUAGES

Native Russian

English Intermediate (B1)

AWARDS



Python for Informatics 06.27.2019



Introduction in Django 02.17.2020

SOCIAL



Freedomdsk



LinkedIn m linkedin.com/in/nikitsenko

Github github.com/JitteryMan

Bitbucket bitbucket.org/jittery

PROFILE



I'm beginner in Python. Study Django on my own. Since 2010 I have been developing apps in Delphi. Create programs, support and develop new functionality for existing applications.

I'm evolving my skills always. Responsible and punctual. Have critical thinking skills.

Phone + 375 (33) 358-13-16



210016 Vitebsk, Belarus



Email freedomdsk@gmail.com



Website jitteryman.github.io/Nikitsenka

WORK EXPERIENCE

2017 - Present O VITEBSK REGIONAL SETTLEMENT AND REFERENCE CENTER

Programming Engineer

Develop and support programs (Borland Delphi 7, Embarcadero Delphi, SQL Firebird)

Developing scripts for automation work in Python

2010 - 2017

VITEBSK STATE TECHNOLOGICAL **COLLEGE**

Programming Engineer

Managed servers, workstations, routers, switches and existing network applications

Supported all LAN, WAN and other networking systems

Created applications (Embarcadero Delphi, Borland C++ Builder)

SKILLS & EXPERTISE

Python	Django	PostgreSQL	MySQL
Delphi	Firebird	SQLite	Git
HTML	CSS	JSON	XML

EDUCATION

2015 - 2019 O VITEBSK STATE TECHNOLOGICAL **UNIVERSITY**

Computer Software Engineering

2007 - 2010 O VITEBSK STATE TECHNOLOGICAL COLLEGE

Computer Software Engineering